Brett Gould

Coding boot camp graduate with a background in various coding languages—primarily JavaScript—developing mobile applications, and building websites from scratch. Professional strengths include creative problem-solving, written and verbal communication, and time management. Detail and deadline oriented mindset from 10+ years of experience in client-focused roles at a top ranked university.

EXPERIENCE

Northwestern School of Professional Studies, Chicago, Illinois (Remote) — *Full Stack Web Development Coding Boot Camp*

November 2021 - May 2022

This immersive six month full stack web development boot camp focused on JavaScript and the MERN stack. During the 24-week course, I attended ten hours of class per week, completed weekly homework assignments, and worked on three group projects that built web and mobile apps from the ground up.

Northwestern Pritzker School of Law, Chicago, Illinois (Remote) — *Associate Director of Donor Relations*

September 2016 - Present

For the past six years, I have worked in a fast-paced, client-focused environment that requires a detail-oriented eye. In this role, I have successfully led many projects from concept to implementation, manipulated and organized complex spreadsheets, developed client-facing deliverables that distill internal jargon into approachable terms, and much more.

Northwestern University, Evanston, Illinois — *Gift Acceptance and Agreements*

June 2010 - September 2016

In this role I wrote the gift agreements for much of Northwestern University's schools and units. Many of my colleagues believed I had a law degree based on my work product and, in fact, I was replaced by an attorney when I left.

EDUCATION

Northwestern School of Professional Studies, Chicago, Illinois (Remote) — *Full Stack Web Development Coding Boot Camp*

Completed May 2022

Illinois State University, Normal, Illinois — Bachelor of Science - Communications, Public Relations

Completed August 2009

1127 E Diana Ave Phoenix, AZ 85020 773.677.9336 BrettDGould@gmail.com github.com/bgould86

SKILLS

- Computer Science Applied to JavaScript
- Databases (MySQL, MongoDB)
- Server Side Development (MERN Stack)
- Browser Based Technologies (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Progressive Web Applications)
- Deployment and Delivery (Heroku, Git, GitHub Pages)
- API Design (Client-Server Model, API, Rest, JSON, AJAX, HTTP request methods, GraphQL)
- Quality Assurance (Unit Testing, Linting, Continuous Integration)
- Other Skills of Note (Adobe Creative Suite, Strong Professional Writing and Communication, Presentations)